allentrepreneurinfo.com 2010-12-31

# Entrepreneurial and Business Related Articles

All Entrepreneur Info Privacy Policy

**Introduction**   

All Entrepreneur Info respects each individual’s right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at All Entrepreneur Info’s Web site. 

**Part I.   Information Collection**   
All Entrepreneur Info collects information through our Web site at several points.  We collect the following information about primary visitors: ip address, browser type and referral URL's.

We may also collect names, and emails on a voluntary basis only, which our users divulge about other people, [such as referrals or gift purchases.] All Entrepreneur Info does not actively market to children, and we never knowingly ask a child under 13 to divulge personal information.

We collect the following general data that is not personally identifiable information: browser type, country and operating system.  We collect demographic data in order to determine where in the world our visitors are from. 

We do not verify the accuracy of this information.

We collect this information through registration forms, and automatic logging files.  Personal information such as name and email is collected through voluntary basis only.  Other information such as ip address, country, and operating system is collected through automatic logging files.   To receive our information, name and email is mandatory because we want to be sure the correct person receives our information.  Other information we request is optional. 

We do employ cookies. A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable All Entrepreneur Info to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users.  Our cookies do have an expiration date. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. 

Banner advertising appearing on our Web site may collect the following information: Referring URL, ip address and browser type.  Third parties collect the following information at our Web site ip address and referring URL.

**Part II.   Information Usage.   
**The information collected by All Entrepreneur Info will be used for sending information to those requested and keeping our visitors informed.  Users who provide information will receive free information, email announcements and/or advertisements. 

Registered users may receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

The information we collect may be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history.  We will not supplement information collected at our Web site with data from other sources.

We may share data with the following third parties: credit card companies.  These third parties will use the information as follows: validate any online purchases.  Users may opt out to have their information shared with third parties.

We offer links to other Web sites.  Please note: When you click on links to other Web sites, we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  Their standards may differ from ours.

Our Web site may one day offer forums or message boards.  Please be advised that information posted in these venues becomes public knowledge. 

If our policy on information collection or uses changes, will advise you by email.

**Part III.   Access to Information   
**All Entrepreneur Info maintains the accuracy of our information by a list manager.  Users may access their own personal information and contact us about inaccuracies they may find by contacting us via a form on the web site.  Users may delete their information from our database by clicking the opt out link at the end of any email correspondence from us.

**Part IV. Problem Resolution   
**If problems arise, users may contact All Entrepreneur Info by the contact form on the web site.  We are committed to resolving disputes within 21 days.

**Part V. Data Storage and Security  
**All Entrepreneur Info protects user information with the following security measures: restricted access, secure servers and firewalls.
